[LAUGHS]
(Stuart:)But if you're dead set
on a comic book, try this.
Oh. "Hellblazer. " What's this about?
(Stuart:)A morally ambiguous confidence man
who smokes, has lung cancer...
(Stuart:)...and is tormented
by the spirits of the undead.
(Penny:)Well, if that doesn't make me
the favorite aunt, I don't know what will.
(Penny:)Is this me?
(Stuart:)Depends. Do you like it?
- Wow, it's really good.
- Yes, that's you.
(Penny:)That's so sweet.
But what if I didn't like it?
(Stuart:)It'd still be you, but I'd feel like an idiot.
(Leonard:)I don't believe it.
Stuart's putting the moves on Penny.
(Howard:)I have got to learn how to draw.
(Penny:)Hey.
(Sheldon:)Once again, defeated
by your own prurient interests.
(Raj:)Guys, have you seen Stuart all up
in Penny's business over there?
(Leonard:)Nobody's up in anybody's business.
Let's just buy our stuff and go.